Recently I was preparing to go for a
cousin's wedding but unfortunately the wedding was cancelled
due to floods and excessive
rains in our city.  Well, things like bad
weather and damage at the venue are some uncertain
and unforeseen situations which can cause a lot
of financial loss.  But think about the couple
and the family who have to undergo this
financial stress.  Well in India wedding
is a big event for every family where
people spend their entire savings and
lifetime earnings for it.  In case of
cancellation of wedding or any event due to any uncertain things such as bad
weather, when you getting
burnt, accidental injury to any
guest and the third party damage to guest and
vendor can cause a lot of financial losses
to the organizers of the event.  Since it is very
important to have an event insurance in
place to insure the most important
event of one's life, the wedding.  Event
Insurance by ICICI Lumber offers you
coverage for losses and damages due to defined
periods up to the sum insured mentioned in the
policy.  Well, Now Weather It's a Music Show,
Award Ceremony, Wedding Conference and Any
Special Event Such as Navratri Puja and
Durga Puja We Have Got You Covered.  Now if it is an
event worth celebrating, it is an
event worth insuring.  Now let us see the key
coverage areas of the event insurance
policy offered by ICICI Lo LBAT.  First,
event cancellation due to fire and allied
perils such as earthquake, burglary and theft
at the venue and due to national and state
casualties, second, event cancellation due to the death of a prominent
figure and third, event cancellation due to the
unexplained failure of a named person to appear for
the event due to any of the contingencies
like death or illness.  Second section which is
material damage.  Now This section offers you a
cover for direct physical loss and damage to
the insured property due to fire including earthquake,
burglary and theft at
the venue. Third and very important personal
accident cover. Now The policy can also offer
you coverage for named persons, blood relations and
relatives against the risk of accidental
death and any injury on the site of the event. Fourth
Public Liability: Liability towards
the third parties for accidents which may
result in injury and damage at the
event venue during the policy period.
Well, we believe in understanding our
clients. Thirdly, here is what we need from you
to tailor this perfect wedding
event insurance plan. First, profile
of the assured and the proposal. Second,
experience details for organizing this
type of insured event. In case of an event manager, an
event manager is available.  Third cover wise some
insured proposed which can be chosen
by the proposal.  Fof Venue and the Complete
Details with the Brief Details of Address.
Sixth safety and security arrangements
for the venue.  And seventh claim details
for any of the events which has happened in
the past.  Now When It Comes to the Claims
and Loss Management.  We've got you covered
with the robust system in place by offering.
First, a 24/7 call center for immediate
assistance.  Second, you can also
directly intimate to our relationship
manager.  And we also provide a huge
network of surveyors and
investigators.  Such SR partners like
Purdy Crawford & Cunningham Lancy
International Pvt Ltd which are well
established in the world of serving.
Also with an immediate deputation of
surveyors within the 24 hours of loss
We make your journey very easy with ICICI
Lombard Now your celebrations are not just
events, there are moments protected by
us Experience a very free event with
ICICI Lombard where your safety is our
priority